Guide to the Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings
Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings
- Office Records, 1948-1971; 1948 1971
  - Draftsmen, engineers, delineators, interior decorators, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Employees: Prospective draftsmen, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fees, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - First State Bank (formerly the Bank of Reidsville), 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Furnishings Proposal Forms (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Godwin Insurance Agency, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Instant Data Access Control, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Jennings (Richard) correspondence, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Name plate: Loewenstein, Atkinson & Woodroof Architects, A.I.A. (Box 29)
  - North Carolina State College: Development Council Report, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - On the job training, 1948-1956 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Ordinance: Town of Leaksville, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Painting and decoration, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Pending file, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Churches (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Industrial (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Residences (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Schools (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Power Oil Company, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Proposal Forms, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Prospective Clients, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Prospective Clients, 1964-1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Prospective Clients (1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Prospective Clients (2 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Prospective Clients, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Public Housing, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Questionnaire (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Residential specification forms (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Servomation of Greensboro, Inc., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Stamp: A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Registered Architect (Box 29)
  - Woodroof and Associates corporation changes, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Woodroof and MacRae Architects: Financial statements, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Woodroof and MacRae Architects: Miscellaneous documents, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Woodroof, MacRae, Senell promotional material (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Ziegler and Company, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Zoning ordinance for Greensboro, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Professional Papers, 1956-1977; 1956 1977
  Professional papers contain general materials relating to architecture and design, such as publications from the American Institute of Architects and other professional organizations, catalogs, brochures, and clippings.
  - American Institute of Architects, North Carolina Chapter, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - American Institute of Architects, North Carolina Chapter (1 of 2), 1958-1966 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - American Institute of Architects, North Carolina Chapter (2 of 2), 1958-1966 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - American Institute of Architects, North Carolina Chapter: Minutes, newsletters, memoranda, 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - American Institute of Architects: Members, officers, structure and services, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - American Institute of Architects: Newsletters, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - American Institute of Architects: Publications, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Architect-engineer questionnaire, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Armco (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Branch banks (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Brochures: Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Catalogs: Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs: Office supply and equipment, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Church architectural data sheets (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Church equipment and supplies (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Church literature, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Church planning: General information, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Church symbols (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Churches, Lutheran: General information, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Cost of buildings, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Costs and Trends, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Dale Blosser and Associates (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Dick and Kirkman, Inc., 1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Dynaturf (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Federal Housing Administration: Minimum Property Requirements, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Fire Station design, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - General Services Administration, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Greensboro Registered Architects, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Investors Diversified Services, Inc.: Annual report, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Josarah Enterprise (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - List of licensed general contractors, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Mailing list, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - McDaniel Lewis and Company: Investment bulletin, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, publications, 1968-1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Modular Building Standards Association (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - North Carolina Board of Architecture, 1966-1971 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - North Carolina Design Foundation, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - North Carolina Licensing Board for Contractors, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Parking Structures (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Planning Note, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Power Oil Company, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Practice of Architecture, 1966-1971 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Practice of Architecture, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Property Control and Construction Manual, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Publications, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Roster of architects, North Carolina Chapter, 1970-1977 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - School planning (1 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - School planning (2 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - School planning (3 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - School planning (4 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Signage (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Standard Master Maker (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - State Board of Examiners of Electrical Contractors, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Structural Steel Specifications, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Systems construction, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Unemployment insurance (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Unemployment insurance (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Uniform System for Construction Specifications, Data Filing, and Cost Accounting, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Faculty and staff directory, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Whitley, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Personal Papers, 1938-1977; 1938 1977
  Personal papers contain correspondence and financial records for both men. Materials in this collection range in date from 1927 to 1977.
  - Automobile: 1957 Buick Riviera, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Christmas cards and gifts, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Insurance, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Investments, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Motels, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Poe family genealogy (Tube 191)
  - Travel brochures (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Trial balance sheet, 1969-1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Woodroof (Albert C.) accounts, notes, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Woodroof (Albert C.) bank statements, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Woodroof (Albert C.) correspondence, 1959-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Woodroof (Albert C.) residence, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) bank statements (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) bank statements (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) correspondence, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) financial records, 1959-1962 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) financial records, 1966-1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) investment club, 1956-1959 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Jr.) paid bills, 1968-1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Sr.) bank statements, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Sr.) financial records, 1974-1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Woodroof (Albert C., Sr.) paid bills, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Woodroof (Mary and Albert) tax information, 1969 (Legalbox 28, Folder 1)
  - Woodroof (W. A.) estate, 1950-1951 (Legalbox 28, Folder 2)
  - Woodroof family genealogy (Tube 192)